pandanda.com 2012-10-02

# Pandanda - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy - October 22, 2008

Pandanda is owned and operated by Sunleaf Studios LLC in Redmond, Washington. Pandanda is intended to be a fun and entertaining place for children to play online so it is of utmost importance to us that your personal information is properly safeguarded. To that end we are in accordance with the United States Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and other applicable legislation regarding privacy laws. This privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to help you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. 

1.) The Information We Gather

During initial registration for a free account we collect the following information; a) child’s account username (which is used as the display name for the child’s Panda avatar and should never be the real name of the child) b) the parent’s email address c) the child’s password to protect the account. The parent’s email address is necessary to activate the account as well as to be able to communicate information regarding the account as in the event of a forgotten username or password and to communicate relevant information pertaining to Pandanda products and services. 

When a player chooses to become an Elite Member through a paid subscription we will require additional personally identifiable information (“PII”) from the parent such as credit card billing information and billing address. This financial information is required for processing payments to Pandanda, but we do not store this information. The financial information you provide is retained by the vendor we employ to process payments for our Elite memberships and for no other purpose. 

In addition to the above information we gather non-personally identifiable information from time to time in the form of polls and surveys simply to improve the Pandanda experience for all players. We may ask questions such as a players’ favorite game or their favorite quest. 

Our website offers ways to contact the Pandanda Team to report bugs, make suggestions, or issues regarding technical problems. In some cases an email address is optional and in others required so that we may communicate with you regarding the inquiry. We use the email address provided in these cases for no other purpose. 

Similar to other commercial websites, our website might utilize a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and web server logs to collect information about how our website is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our website, and the screen resolution of your computer, and what web browser is being used (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer). In addition to cookies we also use “Macromedia Flash Local Shared Objects”. This allows us to store information about your child’s Panda (such as clothes it is wearing etc.) so that we can load files quickly and make the experience more enjoyable by cutting down on wait times. 

Overall, the information we gather is intended to keep you informed, maintain your account and make your child’s experience playing Pandanda as enjoyable as possible by providing the best service. 

2.) How We Use and Disclose the Information We Collect

Broadly speaking, we use personally identifiable information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. 

We also use PII to identify players to ban or suspend them for violating the Terms of Use Agreement if they engage in inappropriate conduct. Please read our Terms of Use Agreement for a complete explanation of our rules. 

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties. 

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution. 

3.) How Do We Protect Your Information?

**How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our website may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. 

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

4.) What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

5.) Your Consent

By using our website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. 

6.) Contact Us

Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy by email at [privacy@pandanda.com](mailto:privacy@pandanda.com) or by mail at: 

Sunleaf Studios   
Attn: Privacy Department   
9537 227th Way NE   
Redmond, WA 98053   
USA
